<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">2Q2R</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="scan_qr">Open Scanner</string>

    <string name="last_used">Last used %1$s at %2$s</string>

    <string name="about_2q2r">About 2Q2R</string>
    <string name="about_version">2Q2R Version %1$s</string>
    <string name="about_copyright">© 2016 - Tera Insights, LLC</string>
    <string name="about_license">2Q2R is licensed under %1$s.</string>
    <string name="about_website">For more information, see our %s.</string>
    <string name="about_feedback">We welcome your feedback:&lt;br/&gt;• %1$s&lt;br/&gt;• %2$s</string>
    <string name="about_icons">Some icons used by this application are reproduced from work created and shared by the Android Open Source Project and used according to terms described in the Creative Commons 2.5 Attribution License.</string>

    <string name="link_website">&lt;a href=&quot;http://terainsights.com&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;</string>
    <string name="link_report_a_problem">&lt;a href=&quot;https://fedorahosted.org/freeotp/wiki/ProblemReport&quot;&gt;Report a Problem&lt;/a&gt;</string>
    <string name="link_ask_for_help">&lt;a href=&quot;http://lists.fedorahosted.org/mailman/listinfo/freeotp-devel&quot;&gt;Ask for Help&lt;/a&gt;</string>
    <string name="link_apache2">&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html&quot;&gt;Apache 2.0&lt;/a&gt;</string>

    <string name="scan_instructions">Please hold steady to scan QR</string>
    <string name="error_no_camera">No camera found.</string>
    <string name="error_attaching_camera">Failed to open camera preview.</string>
    <string name="error_no_perms">Camera access denied!</string>
    <string name="camera_required">You must allow camera access to scan QR codes.</string>
    <string name="camera_closed">Camera closed to save battery.</string>
    <string name="reg_confirm">Would you like to register with the following server?</string>
    <string name="auth_confirm">Would you like to authenticate with the following server?</string>
    <string name="double_check_challenge">Please make sure the following characters match those in your browser:</string>

    <string name="invalid_qr_error">The QR you have scanned is not a 2Q2R-compliant key.</string>
    <string name="unknown_server_error">Sorry, but you are not registered with this server.</string>
    <string name="unknown_firebase_error">An authentication request was just received from an unknown server. Perhaps you deleted your key.</string>
    <string name="registration_not_found_error">Sorry, but you do not appear to be registered with this account.</string>
    <string name="corrupted_registrations_error">The registrations for this device are corrupted! Would you like to manually edit the file, or delete it?</string>
    <string name="outdated_device_error">Your device is outdated. Please upgrade to Android 4.4 (KitKat) or newer.</string>
    <string name="key_gen_error">Sorry, there was an error generating a key-pair for your registration. Please make sure your phone has password protection turned on, and try again.</string>
    <string name="key_access_error">Error while retrieving your key! Please double-check to make sure this is the device you decided to authenticate with, and your phone must also have a password in order to access keys securely.</string>
    <string name="existing_registration_error">It appears you already have this device registered to your account, meaning you can just go ahead and use it to authenticate.</string>
    <string name="auth_timeout_error">Sorry, the authentication could not be completed because your phone has not been authorized recently enough. Please lock and unlock your phone, then scan the QR again.</string>
    <string name="registration_gen_error">An error was encountered while producing a registration response for the server. Please try scanning the QR again.</string>
    <string name="authentication_gen_error">An error was encountered while producing an authentication response for the server. Please try scanning the QR again</string>
    <string name="internet_error">Your device is not connected to the internet. Please connect and try again.</string>
    <string name="info_request_error">There was an error while retrieving info from the server.</string>
    <string name="registration_request_error">There was an error while sending the registration to the server.</string>
    <string name="authentication_request_error">There was an error while sending the authentication to the server.</string>
    <string name="bad_counter_error">You just received an expired authentication attempt! This could mean a third party is trying to use your key to verify themselves!</string>

    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="accounts">Accounts</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan</string>
</resources>